### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mattbonaguidi (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

Quantitative Research Economics

Data Analysis

# Certifications

Master of Science in Applied Economics

# Matthew Bonaguidi

Economics & Damages Consultant at Berkeley Research Group, LLC - M.S. in Applied Economics

Washington, District of Columbia, United States

# Summary

Washington DC based Consultant in the Economics & Damages practice of Berkeley Research Group, LLC.

Graduate of the Johns Hopkins University Krieger School of Art & Sciences m, where I obtained a Masters of Science in Applied Economics and declared a formal concentration in Financial Economics.

# Experience

Berkeley Research Group LLC Economics & Damages Consultant May 2022 - Present (1 year) Washington, District of Columbia, United States

Resolution Economics

2 years 8 months

Senior Consultant

August 2021 - May 2022 (10 months)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

- Implementing quantitative methods to evaluate the completeness of data sets (including large data sets)
- Preparing exhibits that present quantitative findings in a consumable manner
- Actively contributing to all processes in the project work plan and ensuring progress of such plans
- Programming in SAS, STATA, and VBA
- Performing and interpreting statistical tests
- Conducting quality assurance of programs and deliverable materials

#### Consultant

August 2020 - July 2021 (1 year)

Washington DC-Baltimore Area

### Analyst

October 2019 - July 2020 (10 months)

Washington DC

# Stifel Financial Corp.

Intern in Public Finance

February 2019 - June 2019 (5 months)

- Monitored client engagements, governing board agendas and minutes in order to service continuing disclosure requirements and ensure compliance with federal regulations
- Maintained tax-analysis spreadsheet composed of historic property values and tax rate data on municipal issuers
- Constructed official transaction documents alongside senior analysts for the purpose of disclosing necessary borrower information
- Balanced and contributed to multiple deals on a daily basis, generating a working knowledge of transaction and lending processes
- Built pitch book presentations by holistically researching firm underwriting history and current financial market data, for the purpose of marketing firm services to clients

# **ASU REACH Institute**

Research Assistant

August 2018 - April 2019 (9 months)

- -Implementing a Student and Parent Intervention program that is focused around promoting social and emotional learning
- -Interacting with local students to administer multiple student assessment tests
- Gathering public sociodemographic data that helped characterize the representative nature of student samples

### City of Phoenix

Research Intern within Community and Economic Development Department

September 2018 - December 2018 (4 months)

Phoenix, Arizona Area

- Provided value to department by gathering public data that effectively shed light on aspects of the Phoenix economy
- Worked diligently alongside department research specialist to fulfill requests made by the department director
- Performed analysis and authored summary reports on economic topics such as Opportunity Zones and the Open Platform Economy

• Gained experience working with large data sets and communicating data interpretations to fellow department members and non-technical audiences

ZogSports
Sports Program Intern
May 2017 - July 2017 (3 months)
Washington D.C. Metro Area

- -Conducted program outreach to prospective partners for business promotion and event organization
- -Utilized Microsoft Excel to create up to date and formulated schedules
- -Maintained profiles for network contacts that were essential to business expansion
- -Ran company social media pages, successfully carrying out marketing tactics and increasing page impressions
- -Gained conceptual understanding for ideas of social and charitable entrepreneurship
- -Collaborated with colleagues to streamline inventory calculations and the customer registration process

# Education

Johns Hopkins University Advanced Academic Programs

Master of Science - M.S., Applied Economics, with a concentration in Financial

Economics · (2019 - 2021)

Arizona State University - W. P. Carey School of Business Economics (B.S.), Economics · (2017 - 2019)

The Catholic University of America (2015 - 2017)